HEIDI TIRRO

23 Birch Drive Sterling, MA 01564 * 508-951-4864 * htirro@me.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Sourcing and Operations specialist with 11+ years of experience. Proficient multitasker with strong ability to meet any deadline. Would thrive in fast paced environment. Looking to find an organization with a great employee environment with the hopes to be promoted within.

CORE SKILLS

- Reliability
- Researcher / Purchaser
- Communication
- Excel
- Operations
- Admin / Coordinator
- Astea
- Salesforce
- FieldServio
- Procore
- Estimation

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Commonwealth Electrical Technologies

Assistant Project Coordinator, November 2023-Present

- Work with project managers to manage projects in solar field projects
- Acquire, track and cancel mechanical, dumpsters etc.. rentals for the solar field
- Submit on submittals for approval using Procore
- Change orders
- Tracking of all paperwork for the projects

East Coast Energy Systems, Marlborough, MA (bought out Electronic Environments Company)

Sales Project Coordinator, May 2023-November 2023

- Work with the sales team on fulfilling and coordinating projects. Including coordinating 3rd party vendors and ordering from Generac.
- Creating POs, hold for approval POs, invoicing
- Communicating with the customer regarding estimated delivery times
- Keeping track of the details of every project from handoff from sales to ordering all material and staying aware of details until project completion

Electronic Environments Corporation, Marlborough, MA

Bid Desk & Operations Coordinator, November 2012 - April 2023

- Coordinate and confirm correct parts are ordered for clients and arrive on-time
- Proposal creating and tracking
- Transform job costs forms into service estimates for HVAC, Generator and UPS/Electrical
- Create material requisition forms to be ordered for approved service estimates
- Weekly and monthly reporting from Salesforce
- Expense Statements
- Time card input for HVAC technicians
- Generac unit registration for generators through online portal
- Creating calls in Astea
- Obtains Fire/burning permit where brazing is required to complete HVAC repair
- Technician dispatching
- Planning golf outing
- Trip Planning for High level Executives

Comfort Air Systems HVAC, Framingham, MA

Dispatcher / Coordinator, June 2008 – May 2012

- Souring and purchasing parts for all jobs
- Daily scheduling for all technicians
- Customer service

Rentex, Inc / Computer & Audio Visual Rentals, Boston MA

Call Coordinator / Operations Assistant, November 2005 – May 2008

- Directed clients and customers to proper personnel
- Scheduled drivers for Boston area deliveries and pick up
- Assigning and un-assigning equipment on orders
- Inventory, knowing what equipment has left or has been returned
- Controller for all filling

EDUCATION

PLYMOUTH STATE UNIVERSITY, Plymouth NH

Bachelor of Arts, May 2005

Major: Sociology Major GPA: 2.7

Minor: PsychologyOverall GPA: 2.4

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Knowledge of MS Office
- Five S Trained
- Salesforce Knowledge
- Astea
- FieldServio